Michael K. Null, MBA michael.null@bpmw.net 501-712-6723

Profile

Experienced problem solver, analyst and manager. Enthusiastic about customer service. Familiar with statistical decision-making tools and fluent in using computer technology. Excellent communication and customer service skills. Writes articles on business, quality and organizational culture. Enjoys challenging, dynamic environment. Currently enrolled (through mid-September 2015) in The Iron Yard .Net engineering boot camp, then going on to L-3 Mission Integration Division.

Experience

TEST ENGINEER 3, L-3 COMMUNICATIONS, GREENVILLE TX - SEPTEMBER 2015-PRESENT

Systems Engineering position as part of a team that supports the design, development, test, and integration of the maintenance and support systems for ISR aircraft platforms and ground systems.

.NET ENGINEERING STUDENT, THE IRON YARD, LITTLE ROCK, AR-JUNE -SEPTEMBER 2015

Studied C#, Javascript, HTML/CSS and SQL programming languages, object-oriented programming principles and source control. Used Microsoft Visual Studio 2015. Produced several website and database projects culminating in a final project featuring a complex data model, SQL database and responsive, dynamic HTML front-end interface using Angular JS and Bootstrap.

SECTION CHIEF, US AIR FORCE, MILDENHALL UK — 1991-2011

Progressed from apprentice mechanic to intelligence analysis section chief. Supervised up to twenty highly trained people. Led deployed teams in Iraq and achieved operational successes as an individual and a group—received manager of the quarter award. Earned cash awards for re-writing Air Force wide aircraft maintenance procedures. Throughout this time, modeled technical performance excellence and authentic leadership, received employee of the month award along with many other tokens of recognition.

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT, BEAUDET AVIATION, LITTLE ROCK ARKANSAS - 2014

Key role in launching the company's first US workshop. Took on purchasing, bookkeeping and Human Resources responsibilities.

SENIOR BILINGUAL CALL CENTER AGENT, FIS GLOBAL, LITTLE ROCK ARKANSAS — 2011-2013

The primary go-to example to demonstrate customer service professionalism to clients. Stood out in reliability, effectiveness and compassion. Took on the floor supervisor role and trained as a team lead. Was retained when the company eliminated work section in a major layoff. Left to pursue a graduate degree to take on roles with higher levels of responsibility.

Education and Certification

THE IRON YARD .NET ENGINEERING COURSE, JUNE- SEPTEMBER 2015

MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION—UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL ARKANSAS, 2014, GPA 4.0

Coursework in economics, finance, operations management and entrepreneurship

ASSOCIATE IN APPLIED SCIENCE—COMMUNITY COLLEGE OF THE AIR FORCE, 1998

Aircraft Systems Maintenance Technology

CERTIFIED MANAGER—ICPM, JUNE 2015 MEMBER OF ASQ